





Software Engineer

WHO AM I?

I am a software engineer with a lot of experience in framework development for test automation. After working in an all open source team, I have found my love for it. Sharing and improving work together makes coding fun. I love to learn new things all the time. Recently, I started to get interested in Machine Learning and its uses. In general, I always try to stay positive in life and push my own knowledge.



EXPERIENCE

2019 – 2022 Software Engineer in Test

GitLab Inc.

I was working as a software engineer in test for GitLab. My team and I were developing a framework using Selenium and Capybara for easier test implementation and execution.

Ruby / Selenium / Pact.io

2018 – 2019 **Software Engineer, Test Automation**

Shpock GmbH

I was responsible for implementing a new framework for mobile automated testing. Since the product was mainly used from the app, this was vital for the company.

Node.js / Appium / WebdriverIO

2017 – 2018 Test Automation Engineer

Anecon GmbH

This was my introduction to test automation as a concept. I worked on multiple sites. Due to this, I witnessed a plethora of different projects and automation designs.

C# / Selenium / SAP

EDUCATION

2016 – 2018 **Master's Degree**

University of Applied Sciences, Technikum Wien

I have a masters degree in software development. During my studies I worked on many small and medium sized projects. My master thesis was about quality automation.

2017 ISTQB Foundation Level

Austrian Testing Board

During my first employment in the field of test automation, I got the opportunity to pass my ISTQB

certificate. This is a fundamental software testing certificate.

2011 - 2016 Bachelor's Degree

University of Vienna

My bachelor studies were in the field of health informatics like imaging technologies. My thesis was in the field of medical data collection systems.

LANGUAGES

HOBBIES

NON PROFIT

German - native **Croatian** - native **English** - proficient I love working with wood and improving my own home with it. Also taking pictures of all the things.

My family and I try to help kids in need. Due to war, a lot of children are alone in a new country.